Hello! I'm JP Fairchild.

UX - UI - MOTION DESIGNER

http://jpfairchild.com jpfairchild73@gmail.com (914) 500 3251

Objective



Skills



I love to be challenged, to think outside the box. I want to work for a company that makes meaningful connections with people, where work is easy, because the people I'm working with are as passionate as I am.

I specialize in user experience, visual design, animation, branding, and illustration. I work hard to have a diverse skill set, executing interactive design while maintaining a focus on the user experience.

Work Experience



BROOKLYN UNITED

Interactive & Motion Design Intern (June - Aug 2014)

Worked on a wide variety of client work, from companies like AT&T to local bars, doing branding, animation, and web design.

LAB SENIOR ASSISTANT

Lab Overseer
(Jan 2012 - Present)

I oversee the lab on a daily basis, maintaining the lab and training new lab managers.

DESIGNER SKETCHBOOKS

CEO & UX / UI Designer (Jan 2014 - Present)

Founder and designer of a sketchbook company personally made for designers.

FREELANCE DESIGNER

Iconography, Web Design, And Motion (2011 - Present)

Designer for a wide range of products and services, and consulting for companies on current and future designs.

DESIGNERS SKETCHBOOK

CEO & UX / UI DESIGNER

In January of 2014, I started a company that makes customizable sketchbooks for design professionals. From just me, we now have four employees who continue to grow and innovate our sketchbooks! Feel free to ask me for one, I love to share.

Extracurricular

NEW MEDIA CLUB

Mentor

Mentor in the New Media Club, helping underclassmen understand and solve problems that they have in current classes

RUN FOR THE WILD BRONX ZOO

WCS Staff

Volunteer at The Wildlife Conservation Society to protect wildlife globally

Education

ROCHESTER INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

Major - New Media Design

Minor - Writing

RYE HIGH SCHOOL

High Honors